<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-09T14:42:30-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Benjamin Campagna</title><subtitle>BenJamin since 1998</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Front-End Development Consultant for NestPick.com</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/nestpick" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Front-End Development Consultant for NestPick.com" /><published>2020-01-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-01-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/nestpick</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/nestpick">&lt;p&gt;December, 2020 - Present&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bencampa/ben_site/master/images/nest.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was inspired by an article Nestpick published regarding &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nestpick.com/generation-z-city-index-2019/&quot;&gt; the best cities to live in for Generation Z&lt;/a&gt;. They put together a database that ranked each city in multiple different categories like safety, affordability, etc. They had all of the raw data posted in the article but no good way to organize the information. With matchmaking on my mind from my prior experience at Wizard Match, I had an idea about creating a person to country matchmaker that allowed you to scale the importance of each category. I sent them my idea along with a little mockup using C++ to explain the basic logic of the idea. They loved the idea and are started writing up a statement of work for me to complete the project. I will update this site as the job progresses!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">December, 2020 - Present I was inspired by an article Nestpick published regarding the best cities to live in for Generation Z. They put together a database that ranked each city in multiple different categories like safety, affordability, etc. They had all of the raw data posted in the article but no good way to organize the information. With matchmaking on my mind from my prior experience at Wizard Match, I had an idea about creating a person to country matchmaker that allowed you to scale the importance of each category. I sent them my idea along with a little mockup using C++ to explain the basic logic of the idea. They loved the idea and are started writing up a statement of work for me to complete the project. I will update this site as the job progresses!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Front-End Development Consultant for Wizard Match LLC.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/wizard" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Front-End Development Consultant for Wizard Match LLC." /><published>2019-07-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-07-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/wizard</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/wizard">&lt;p&gt;July 2019 - Present&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bencampa/ben_site/master/_site/images/Wizard_logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Worked with Angular (Web framework) to create a tiered permission and access level comment sections that followed the Redux pattern on a new healthcare-related enterprise website.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Used DevExtreme (HTML application framework) to design a custom pop-up comment section that included both user and date imprinting.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Created extensive Mock Web-API data that helped run and test the website during the development.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Designed and built a complex multi-tiered database that allows comment viewing by both users and employees. Also created a secure access level structure that only allows designated comments to be created and viewed by agency employees.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">July 2019 - Present Worked with Angular (Web framework) to create a tiered permission and access level comment sections that followed the Redux pattern on a new healthcare-related enterprise website. Used DevExtreme (HTML application framework) to design a custom pop-up comment section that included both user and date imprinting. Created extensive Mock Web-API data that helped run and test the website during the development. Designed and built a complex multi-tiered database that allows comment viewing by both users and employees. Also created a secure access level structure that only allows designated comments to be created and viewed by agency employees.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tech Consultant at Campus Computer showcase</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/tech" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tech Consultant at Campus Computer showcase" /><published>2019-05-04T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-05-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Tech</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/tech">&lt;p&gt;May 2019 - Present&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bencampa/ben_site/master/_site/images/tech.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Assisted faculty, staff and students with their usage of all technology provided in Campus Computing Sites facilities and services as well as personal device support usually with software issues, data transfers, and malware/virus removal&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Troubleshot site hardware and re-image machines&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Troubleshot and performed maintenance to printers and other sites equipment&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fostered a productive and positive environment in the site by providing feedback and ideas for improvement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">May 2019 - Present Assisted faculty, staff and students with their usage of all technology provided in Campus Computing Sites facilities and services as well as personal device support usually with software issues, data transfers, and malware/virus removal Troubleshot site hardware and re-image machines Troubleshot and performed maintenance to printers and other sites equipment Fostered a productive and positive environment in the site by providing feedback and ideas for improvement</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Special Projects Intern for TPG Capital</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/TPG" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Special Projects Intern for TPG Capital" /><published>2018-05-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-05-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/tpg</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/TPG">&lt;p&gt;May 2018 - September 2018&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bencampa/ben_site/master/images/tpg.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Worked directly with TPG Chief Economist David Bailey on several projects to help better understand the macroeconomic factors affecting TPG’s $84B private equity portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Created elaborate Excel macros to interact directly with Bloomberg data feeds in order to display 94 unique economic data points for the 18 focus countries being analyzed.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Collaborated with the TPG economic team to analyze data, automate trend deviation notifications and create predictive pricing models.)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">May 2018 - September 2018 Worked directly with TPG Chief Economist David Bailey on several projects to help better understand the macroeconomic factors affecting TPG’s $84B private equity portfolio. Created elaborate Excel macros to interact directly with Bloomberg data feeds in order to display 94 unique economic data points for the 18 focus countries being analyzed. Collaborated with the TPG economic team to analyze data, automate trend deviation notifications and create predictive pricing models.)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Leadership Fellow at Barger Leadership Institute</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/BLI" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Leadership Fellow at Barger Leadership Institute" /><published>2017-09-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-09-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/BLI</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/BLI">&lt;p&gt;September 2017 - Present&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bencampa/ben_site/master/images/BLI.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Organized a case study project focused on deepening understanding of intrinsic motivation and identifying factors with the greatest impact on collegiate learning.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Led project team responsible for interviewing faculty members and business leaders.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Coordinated a campus-wide campaign based on study results and interviews to promote more effective academic practices.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">September 2017 - Present Organized a case study project focused on deepening understanding of intrinsic motivation and identifying factors with the greatest impact on collegiate learning. Led project team responsible for interviewing faculty members and business leaders. Coordinated a campus-wide campaign based on study results and interviews to promote more effective academic practices.</summary></entry></feed>